The Charles Shackford Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Writings by Charles Shackford, 1945-1979; Series II; 1' (3 boxes)
  - Paul Hindemith['s] Unterweisung im Tonsatz: III Übungsbuch für den dreistimmigen Satz. -- [1972]., 4 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    Typescript with red, black, and blue ink corrections.
    Review for Notes.
    4 sheets; 28 cm.
    Postcard from Notes laid in.
    p. 451-452; 23 Cm.
    Offprint.
  - Pitch range and the actual pitch of vibrato tones. -- [1960]., 8 [i.e. 10] sheets; 26-28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    "American String Teacher article published April 1960"--Container.
    Includes photocopy of chart.
    5 sheets; 28 cm.
    [4] sheets; 28 cm.
    Typescript and holograph in pencil.
    Charts, etc.
  - Pitch range and the actual pitch of vibrato tones / by Pr. Charles R. Shackford., p. 25, 28; 31 cm. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    From journal: The American string teacher, April, 1960.
  - Quartet music in the country. -- c1979, p. 25-26, 53; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 32)
    In: Music Mountain golden anniversary season [souvenir program].
    p. 10-11; 28 cm.
    In: The Connecticut College alumni magazine, v. 56, no, 4, summer, 1979.
  - [Relation of frequency response to the amplitude modulations accompanying the string instrument vibrato], 8 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - The relation of frequency response to the amplitude modulations accompanying the string instrument vibrato: a paper read by Charles R. Shackford at the International Congress on Acoustics, Cambridge, Massachusetts, June 20, 1956., 5 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Resolution and progression in complex and ambiguous harmony. -- c1976., 23 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 34)
    "Delivered before the National Conference on Music Theory, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, March 1, 1976."--Container.
    "Original Masters"--Container.
    1 sheet of notes with unidentified music sketches on verso laid in.
  - Resolution and progression in complex and ambiguous harmony. -- c1976., 23 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - The role of perception in tonal dynamics., p. 4-5, 7; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 36)
    In: Wilson College bulletin, v. 27, no. 5, April, 1964.
  - [Selections -- 1971 (?)], [51] sheets; 21-32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 37)
    Holograph in ink and pencil and typescript.
    Notes, charts, and drafts for unidentified writings.
    "Hind-Schoen. Feeling"--Container.
  - [Research materials], [12] sheets; 22 x 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 38)
    Articles and extracts from books by George Perle, Josef Rufer, Arnold Schönberg, Hans Heinz Stuckenschmidt, and from a work on At[t?]wood's studies with Mozart.
    "At[t?]wood studies with Mozart"--Container.
  - [Some Aspects of Perception] Some aspects of the perception of tonal material. -- [c1961]., 16 [i.e. 29] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 39)
    Typescript with red and black pencil and ink corrections.
  - Some aspects of perception I: sizes of harmonic intervals in performance. -- c1961., p. 162-202; 24 cm. (Box 15, Folder 39)
    With: Some aspects of perception II.
  - Some aspects of perception I: sizes of harmonic intervals in performance. -- c1961., p. 162-202; 24 cm. (Box 15, Folder 40)
    In: The journal of music theory, v. 2, November, 1961.
  - Some aspects of perception II: interval sizes and tonal dynamics in performance. -- c1962., 10 [i.e. 24] sheets; 16-28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 41)
    Includes 2 sheets of holograph examples in ink.
    Letter to Allen Forte with corrections and addenda laid in.
  - Some aspects of perception II: interval sizes and tonal dynamics in performance. -- c1962., 16 p. 66-90; 24 cm. (Box 15, Folder 39)
    With: Some aspects of Perception I.
  - Some aspects of perception III: Addenda. -- c1962., 9 [i.e. 13] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 42)
    Typescript with corrections in ink.
  - Some aspects of perception III: Addenda. -- c1962., p. 295-303, bound; 24 cm. (Box 15, Folder 43)
    In: The journal of music theory, v. 6, winter 1962.
  - Three lecture recitals on piano sonatas of Ludwig van Beethoven. -- 1955., 4, 3 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 44)
    Dated: "May 10, 1955".
  - [Übungsbuch für den dreistimmigen Satz by Paul Hindemith], [31, 14] sheets; 28-32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 45)
    Holograph in ink with red ink corrections.
  - Übungsbuch für den dreistimmigen Satz by Paul Hindemith edited by Andres Briner, P. Daniel Meier, and Alfred Rubeli / (reviewed by Charles Shackford. -- [1973]., 13 [i.e. 15] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 45)
    Typescript with corrections in black, blue, and red pen.
    Review for the Journal of music theory.
    6 sheets of musical examples and notes laid in
    [11] sheets; 28 cm.
    Typescript with holograph notes (photocopy).
    43 [i.e. 45] sheets; 28 cm.
    p. 238-265; 23 cm.
    Report on Paul Hindemith collection at Yale laid in.
  - Wellesley College Choir has active year. -- 1953., p. 287-288; 30 cm. (Box 15, Folder 46)
    In: Wellesley alumnae magazine, [Wellesley, Massachusetts], July, 1953.
  - [What tragedy?], [40] sheets; 11-28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 47)
    Notes for sermon.
    26 sheets; 28 cm.
  - What tragedy? -- 1966., 7 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 15, Folder 47)
    Dated: "2/13/66"--sheet 1, manuscript
    Two letters from Gordon p. Wiles laid in.
- Correspondence, 1952-1980; Series III; .8' (2 boxes)
  Correspondence is divided into five subseries and is arranged alphabetically by recipient (A and C) or by sender (B, D, and E). Cross-references refer from corporate bodies to individuals or vice versa, and to items outside this series with which some correspondence is laid in. Enclosures are not counted among the number of items.
  - Correspondence from Charles Shackford, III.A
    - Allen, Eugene W., 1975-1978; 6 items (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Allison, William, 1956 Apr. 15; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Althouse, Paul L., 1972 Jan. 31; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Audrey, 1976 Nov. 13; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, G. P., 1972 July 20; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Armstrong, James F., 1962 May 20; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Austin, William, 1966-1976; 9 items (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Barth, Craig T., 1976 Dec. 20; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Batter, Larry, 1978 June-Aug.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Baxter, Lincoln, 1975 Aug.-Nov.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Belmont Music Publishers, 1972 June 15; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Belwin Mills, 1972 June-Dec.; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Berkshire String Quartet (Box 16, Folder 4)
      See: Magg, Fritz and Rossi, Urico.
    - Berry, Wallace T., 1968-1969; 4 items (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bingham, Susan H., 1970 Apr.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Blanc, Roger, 1975-1979; 5 items (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Boatwright, Howard, 1969 June 3; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Browne, Richmond, 1976 Feb.-Mar.; 4 items (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bushnell, Alyssa, 1979 Feb. 14; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Wally, 1978 Jan.-Feb.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Campe, Mrs. Robert H., Jr., 1971 Jan.-Mar.; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Carter, Dianne, 1978 June-Sept.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Cohen, Arthur, 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Cohen, Chip, 1976 Dec. 20; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Cohen, Isidore, 1976-1977; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut College, 1968-1974; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 7)
      See also: Althouse, Paul L., Anderson, Audrey, Armstrong, James F., Dale, Clair, Detmold, John, Eastburn, Warrine E., Eversole, James E., Shain, Charles E., and Thomson, Margaret L.
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 16, Folder 7)
      See: Delponte, Joanne and Keller, Anthony S.
    - Cummings, Anna F., 1961 June 25; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Dale, Clair, 1976 Mar. 12; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Dana, Charles A., 1969 Dec. 1; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - D'Arms, Edward F. (Box 16, Folder 8)
      See: Ford Foundation.
    - The Day [New London], 1974-1978; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Delponte, Joanne, 1976 Mar.-Oct.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Detmold, John, 1973 Nov. 21; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Dimmock, "Petie", 1969 May 19; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Dunn, Thomas, 1969-1970; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Eastburn, Warrine E., 1968 Sept.-Dec.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Englebardt, Lynn and Connie Smith, 1978 Dec. 17; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Eversole, James A., 1976 Nov. 23; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Faber and Faber, 1972 June 15; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Fansler, Thomas, 1979 Feb. 14; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Fay, Thomas, 1970 Apr. 22; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Fiedler, Arthur, 1971 Mar. 5; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Filosa, Albert, 1971 Feb.-Mar.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - The First Parish Unitarian Church [Arlington, Massachusetts] (Box 16, Folder 10)
      See: Cummings, Anna F.
    - Ford Foundation, 1961-1668 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
      Correspondence and enclosures concerning grants.
      Includes: 5 letters to Edward F. D'Arms, drafts of proposals, letters of recommendation from Bruce Simonds and Louise Perry, and research data.
    - Forte, Allen, 1960-1961; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 13)
      See also: II. Writings. Some aspects of perception II.
    - Friend, Owen L., 1972 July 28; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Fuller, Albert, 1970-1976; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Fuller, Myrtice, 1959 Aug. 17; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Goldberg, Anne, 1979 Apr. 13; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Grasso, Ella, 1975 Mar. 28; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1976 Jan.-Oct. (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Application for grant and related material.
      Includes 1 letter to Stephen L. Schlesinger.
    - Hancock, Gerre, 1972 Feb. 8; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Hartford Symphony (Box 16, Folder 14)
      See: Winograd, Arthur.
    - Hermann, Virginia Hitchcock, 1965 May 24; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Herrmann, William, 1969 June-Dec.; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Hewlett-Packard Company (Box 16, Folder 14)
      See: Slade, Stuart C.
    - Hollander, Laurie J., 1975 Apr. 30; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - The Hopkins Grammar School (Box 16, Folder 15)
      See: Richmann, Herbert E.
    - Hurwood, David L., 1976-1977; 4 items (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Husa, Karel, 1976 May 28; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Journal of Music Theory (Box 16, Folder 15)
      See: Allen Forte and Brian Simms.
    - Karas, Joza, 1970 Mar. 5; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Keller, 1970 Dec. 3; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kilmer, Richard, 1971 Jan. 26; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kirkpatrick, John, 1976 Jan. 20; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kobler, Donald, 1977-1979; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - [Kodis], Ralph, 1975 Feb. 18; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - KUT-FM [Austin, Texas] (Box 16, Folder 16)
      See: Lustig, Leila.
    - Kwartin, Paul, 1977 Jan.-Sept.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Lockwood, Lewis (Box 16, Folder 16)
      See: II. Writings by Charles Shackford. "Imitatio" in Dufay's missa Se la face ay pale.
    - Lord, Brian, 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Lurtsema, Robert, 1976 Jan. 15; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Lustig, Leila, 1978 Aug. 14; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - McPhee, John, 1971-1977; 4 items (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Magg, Fritz, 1978 Apr.-Jul.; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Marlboro Music Festival (Box 16, Folder 18)
      See: Cohen, Isidore and Serkin, Rudolf.
    - Meier, Gustav, 1970-1975; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Morse, Rose, 1972 June 15; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Music Mountain (Box 16, Folder 18)
      See: Kobler, Don, Magg, Fritz, and Rossi, Urico.
    - Newton-Wellesley Hospital (Box 16, Folder 18)
      See: Fuller, Myrtice.
    - Newcomb, Anthony, 1974 Apr. 15; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - The New Yorker, 1965-1971; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 19)
      See also: McPhee, John, Sargeant, Winthrop, and Whitaker, Rogers E.M.
    - Paine, Thomas, 1973 Oct. 19; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Phemister, William, 1977 June 24; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Pine, Mitchell, 1977 May 25; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Piston, Walter, 1974-1976; 15 items (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Pollack, Howard, 1977 Oct. 30; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Pundit [Connecticut College] (Box 16, Folder 20)
      See: Anderson, Audrey.
    - Reinecke, Hans-Peter (Box 16, Folder 20)
      See: B. To Charles Shackford. Reinecke, Hans-Peter.
    - [Rey, Walter], "Teddy", 1978 Feb. 1; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Richard, Peter, 1978 June 2; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Richmann, Herbert E., 1959 June 10; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Rolland, Paul, 1960 Mar. 21; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Rosenbaum, Robert A., 1969 June 2; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Rossi, Urico, 1976-1978; 8 items (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Saint Thomas Church [New York] (Box 16, Folder 22)
      See: Hancock, Geere.
    - Sargeant, Winthrop, 1965 Mar. 8; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Schlesinger, Stephen L. (Box 16, Folder 22)
      See: Guggenheim Foundation.
    - The School of Nursing, Newton Wellesley Hospital (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Schultz, Theodore, 1974-1976; 6 items (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Schwartz, Elliot, 1976 Nov. 23; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Serkin, Rudolf, 1976 Jul.-Sept.; 4 items (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - [Sewall], Richard, 1972-1978; 10 items (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - [Shackford], Martha [Hale], 1961 Feb. 22; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - [Shackford, William], "Bill", 1971-1973; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Shain, Charles E., 1966-1973; 6 items (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Simms, Brian, 1972-1973; 7 items (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - [Simonds], Bruce, 1976-1977; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Slade, Stuart C., 1965 Feb. 24; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Connie (Box 16, Folder 27)
      See: Englebardt, Lynn and Connie Smith.
    - Sparks, Edgar H., 1974 May 20; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Stoney, William, 1967 Jan. 25; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Sullivan, Raymond A. (Box 16, Folder 27)
      See: Translations Center, [Brooklyn College].
    - Tapley, Roland, 1971 Jan. 21; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Thomson, Margaret L., 1972-1973; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Translations Center, [Brooklyn College], 1974 May-Sept.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - United States Army,Band (Box 16, Folder 28)
      See: Allen, Eugene W.
    - Vadala, Christopher, 1973 Apr. 30; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Van Sickle, Howard M., 1960 July 12; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Wade, John P., 1977 Mar. 5; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Waite, William, 1977 Dec. 1; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Walters, Larry, 1978 Dec. 7; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Weicker, Lowell P., Jr., 1977 Nov. 29; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Weinrich, Carl, 1952 Oct. 14; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Wesleyan University [Connecticut] (Box 16, Folder 29)
      See: Rosenbaum, Robert A.
    - WFCR [Amherst] (Box 16, Folder 29)
      See: Cohen, Arthur.
    - WGBH [Boston] (Box 16, Folder 29)
      See: Lurtsema, Robert.
    - Whitaker, Rogers E. M., 1975 Mar. 13; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Wilson, Keith, 1973-1976; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Winograd, Arthur, 1970-1979; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Winslow, Richard K., 1968 Jan. 17; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Wood, James, 1976 Nov. 1; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - WVHF [Hartford] (Box 16, Folder 29)
      See: Brian Lord.
    - W.W. Norton, 1972 June 15; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Yale University (Box 16, Folder 29)
      See: Fay, Thomas, Forte, Allen, Journal of Music Theory, Meier, Gustav, Simms, Brian, Simonds, Bruce, and Waite, Wiliam.
    - Youngholm, Philip, 1979 Apr. 13; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Zaslaw, Neal, 1972 June-Oct.; 4 items (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - "Jim", 1973 Aug. 13; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - "Mollie", 1977 Jan. 15; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to Charles Shackford, III.B
    - Alan, Don, 1964 Jan. 3; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Alexander, Valerie, 1956 June 21; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 30)
      For enclosed photographs, see: V.A Photographs. Charles Shackford alone.
    - Allen, Eugene W., 1978 Aug. 7; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - [Althouse], Paul, [1972], June 5; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - American String Teachers Association (Box 16, Folder 30)
      See: Rolland, Paul and Van Sickle, Howard M.
    - Anderson, E. Ruth, 1973 July; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Armstrong, James, 1965-1975; 5 items (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Ashway, Mildred, 1964 Jan. 9; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Atlas, David, 1963 May 1; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Austin, William W., 1955-1976; 10 items (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Babcock, Henry H., 1956 May 21; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Bachrach, Fabian, 1961-1962; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - The Band of the Grenadier Guards (Box 16, Folder 31)
      See: Parkes, Peter W.
    - Barth, Craig T., 1976 Oct. 14; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Bartow, Nevett (Box 16, Folder 31)
      See: I.C Music by Others. Bartow, Nevett. The tower of Babel.
    - Baxter, Lincoln, 1975-[1977 (?)]; 4 items (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Belmont Community Chorus (Box 16, Folder 31)
      See: Irene Daitch.
    - Belwin Mills, 1972 June-Dec.; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Bennett, Beatrice, 1960 May 25; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - [Bennett Junior College], "B.K.", 1945-1946; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - [Bennett Junior College], "Jack", [ca. 1945]; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Berry, Wallace T., 1968-1969; 5 items (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Bingham, [Susan H. (?)], 1969-1970; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Blanc, Roger, 1975-1978; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Boatwright, Howard, 1969 Mar. 21; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Bowdoin College (Box 16, Folder 33)
      See: Tillotson, Frederic.
    - Boyden, David D., 1956 Feb. 7; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Bozyan, H. Frank, [1956-1961 (?)]; 6 items (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation (Box 16, Folder 33)
      See: Corden, Kenneth.
    - Brooks, Charles F., 1954-1957; 2 items (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Browne, Richmond, 1975-1976; 3 items (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Campbell, Wallace, 3rd, 1977-1978; 5 items (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Campe, Jean George, 1971 Feb. 23; 1 item (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Chirurg, Virginia B., 1953 Apr. 9; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Church, Frank, 1978 Aug. 23; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Clarke, Melville, Jr., 1962 Sept. 26; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Coffin, William Sloane, Jr., 1960 Aug. 14; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Cohen, Arthur R., 1970 Dec. 1; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Cohen, Isidore, [1976 Summer]; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Connecticut College (Box 17, Folder 34)
      See: Althouse, Paul L., Armstrong James, Church, Frank, Connecticut College Faculty ("Bill","Helen"), Dale, Clair, Dendy, James, Eastburn, Warrine, Jordan, Philip H., Jr., Seng, Peter J., and Shain, Charles E.
    - [Connecticut College Faculty], "Bill", [1968] Nov. 7; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - [Connecticut College Faculty], "Helen", 1978 Oct. 11; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Conover, John H., 1958 May 16; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Conybeare, Lynne, 1973 Jan. 31; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Coolidge, John C., 1977 Nov. 11; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Corden, Kenneth, 1966 Jan.-Mar.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Cornell University (Box 17, Folder 36)
      See: Austin, William and Husa, Karel.
    - Cronin, James E., 1969 May 16-23; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Daitch, Irene, 1956 Jan.-May; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Dale, Clair, 1976 Mar. 8; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - d'Armand, John B., 1973 Oct. 25; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - d'Arms, Edward (Box 17, Folder 37)
      See: The Ford Foundation.
    - [Davison, Archibald T.], "Doc", 1947 Aug. 15; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Deguise, Alice, [1978 Mar.]; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Deguise, [Pierre] and [Rita] Terras, 1977 May 23; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Delponte, Joanne, 1976 mar. 17; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - [Dendy, James], "Jim", 1961 June 23; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - [Dimmock], "Pete", 1969 Sept. 3; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Ducibella, Salvatore F., 1967 Mar. 1; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Duckles, Vincent, 1956 Apr. 3; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Dunn, Thomas, 1955-1956; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Eastburn, Warrine, 1968 Aug.-Dec.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Ell, Frank Wm., 1979 Mar. 9; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - [Englebardt, Lynn and Connie Smith], "Lynn and Connie", 1978; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Faber and Faber, 1972 July 6; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Felsen, Mrs. David, 1973 Dec. 10; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - First Congregational Church, Natick, Mass., 1954-1956; 4 items (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - The First Parish Unitarian Church, Arlington, Massachusetts (Box 17, Folder 39)
      See: Bennett, Beatrice.
    - The First Presbyterian Church, Carlisle, Pennsylvania (Box 17, Folder 39)
      See: Weer, Russell M.
    - The Ford Foundation, 1961-1968; 14 items (Box 17, Folder 40)
      Includes letters from Marcia T. Thompson, Joseph M. McDaniel, Jr., and Edward d'Arms.
    - Forte, Allen, 1960-1962; 14 items (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - French, [Richard F.], 1947 Dec. 3; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Fuchs, William, 1977 Jan. 14; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Fuller, Myrtice L., 1959 May 19; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Fuller, Susie, [1971] Dec. 20; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Gerber, Maynard, 1975 Mar. 13; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Grasso, Ella, 1976 Dec. 9; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Grout, Donald J., 1960 Dec. 7; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - G. Schirmer, Inc. (Box 17, Folder 42)
      See: I.A Music by Charles Shackford. Blessed is the man (1971).
    - Hartford Symphony (Box 17, Folder 42)
      See: Philion, Thomas E. and Winograd, Arthur.
    - Harvard University, Department of Music (Box 17, Folder 42)
      See: Davison, Archibald T., French, Richard F., Piston, Walter, Vosgerchian, Luise, and Woodworth, G. Wallace.
    - Harvard University, Blue Hill Meteorological Observatory (Box 17, Folder 42)
      See: Brooks, Charles F. and Conover, John H.
    - Hewlett-Packard Company (Box 17, Folder 42)
      See: Smith, W. Edwin.
    - Herrmann, William A., 1969 July-Nov.; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Hindemith, Paul, 1942-1954; 10 items (Box 17, Folder 43)
      Greeting cards, artwork by Hindemith.
    - Hultherg (?), Lois, 1961 June 12; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Human Relations Area Files, 1956 Jan. 12; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Hurwood, David L., 1976-1978; 10 items (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Husa, Karel, 1976 May 11; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Jacobs, Harold, [1969, Summer]; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Jacobson, George H., 1972 July- Oct.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Jenks, Deborah, 1967 June 2; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Jones, James S., 1965 Apr. 29; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Jordan, Philip H., Jr., 1973 Apr. 29; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Journal of Music Theory (Box 17, Folder 46)
      See: Browne, Richard, Forte, Allen, and Simms, Brian R.
    - Keller, Anthony S., 1970-1977; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Kihl, Elizabeth W., 1978 Sept. 14; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Kobler, [Donald], 1977-1979; 6 items (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Kodis, Ralph D., 1975 Feb. 9; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - KUT-FM, Austin (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Kuttner, Fritz A., 1962 Nov.-Dec.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 47)